I always dream of being.أحلم دوما أن أكون.
The best of all.الأفضل بين الجميع.
So I collect Pokémon.لذا أجمع البوكيمون.
The best I can.على خير الصنيع.
I always dream of being.أحلم دوما من أن أكون.
The best of all.الأفضل بين الجميع.
So I collect Pokémon.لذا أجمع البوكيمون.
The best I can.على خير الصنيع.
I'm going to travel across Earth.سأسافر عبر الأرض.
searchering everywhere.باحثًا في كل مكان.
For Pokémon, the peace Tool.عن بوكيمون أداة السلام.
An unrelenting force (Pokémon I'll collect now).قوةٌ لا تهان (بوكيمون سأجمعها الآن).
Support me (Pokémon).فلتساندني (بوكيمون).
With your strength help me? (Pokémon)بقوتك ساعدني؟ (بوكيمون)
Oh to our only dream.آه لحلمنا الوحيد.
Towards a New World (Towards a New World).نحو عالم جديد (نحو عالمٍ جديد).
(Pokémon, I'll collect it now).بوكيمون، سأجمعها الآن).
To support goodness.لنصرة الخير.
To rebel evil from others.لدحر الشر عن الغير.
Teach me, and take Pokémon from me (Pokémon).علمني، وخذ مني بوكيمون (بوكيمون).
(I'll collect it now).سأجمعها الآن).
I always dream of being.أحلم دوما أن أكون.
The best of all.الأفضل بين الجميع.
So I gather Pokémon.لذا أجمع البوكيمون.
The best I can.على خير الصنيع.
I'm going to travel across Earth.سأسافر عبر الأرض.
searchering everywhere.باحثًا في كل مكان.
For Pokémon, the peace Tool.عن بوكيمون أداة السلام.
An unfailing force.قوةٌ لا تهان.
(Pokémon, I'll collect it now).(بوكيمون، سأجمعها الآن).
Please support me.فلتساندني.
With your strength help me (Pokémon).بقوتك ساعدني (بوكيمون).
Oh to our only dream.آه لحلمنا الوحيد.
Towards a New World (Towards a New World).نحو عالمٍ جديد (نحو عالمٍ جديد).
(Pokémon, I'll collect it now).بوكيمون، سأجمعها الآن).
To support goodness.لنصرة الخير.
To rebel evil from others.لدحر الشر عن الغير.
Teach me and take it from me.علمني وخذ مني.
Pokemon (Pokémon, I'll collect it now).بوكيمون (بوكيمون، سأجمعها الآن).
I'll collect it now (Pokémon).سأجمعها الآن (بوكيمون).
Where is my ball? In the center of the field. I lost my ball. How will I play?أين كرتي؟ وسط الملعب. ضاعت كرتي، كيف سألعب؟
Ash, listen to me, Ash.آش آش اسمعني يا آش.
Detective Conan?المحقق كونان؟
discovers the mysterious and exciting.يكتشف الغامض والمثير.
Deduces with his mind a lot.يستنتج بالعقل الكثير.
Conan the little guy, seems confident.كونان الرجل الصغير، يبدو واثقًا.
Detective Conan! Always wins.
المحقق كونان. يربح دائمًا.
Detective Conan, always succeeds.
المحقق كونان. ينجح دائمًا.
Oh Conan, Conan, Conan is smart.آآآآه كونان، كونان، كونان ذكيٌ.
Whoever encourages Conan, Conan, always wins.ومن يشجع كونان، كونان، يربح دائمًا.
No no no no no no (x4).لا لا لا لا لا لاه لا لا لا لاه (×4).
Oh Conan, Conan, Conan is smart.أوووووه كونان، كونان، كونان ذكيٌ.
Whoever encourages Conan, Conan, always wins.ومن يشجع كونان، كونان، يربح دائمًا.
Detective Conan, always wins.المحقق كونان، يربح دائمًا.
Detective Conan, always succeeds.المحقق كونان، ينجح دائمًا.
Oh Conan, Conan, Conan is smart.أوووووه كونان، كونان، كونان ذكيٌ.
Whoever encourages Conan, Conan, always wins.ومن يشجع كونان، كونان، يربح دائمًا.
No no no no no no (x4).لا لا لا لا لا لاه لا لا لا لاه (×4).
Oh Conan, Conan, Conan is smart.أوووووه كونان، كونان، كونان ذكيٌ.
Whoever encourages Conan, Conan, always wins.ومن يشجع كونان، كونان، يربح دائمًا.
Detective Conan, always succeeds.المحقق كونان، ينجح دائمًا.
Detective Conan, always wins.المحقق كونان، يربح دائمًا.
Detective Conan.المحقق كونان.
What do you want, Conan?ماذا تريد يا كونان؟
Mitsy warned me that something is going to happen to you today.ميتسي حذرتني من شيء ما سيحدث هذا اليوم لك.
Since becoming a TV anchor at the children's TV station, Misty has been fantasizing about things that are not true.منذ أن أصبحت ميستي مذيعة في محطة الأطفال التلفزيونية، وهي تتوهم أمورا غير حقيقية.
Mitsy is not delusional. And even if that's the case, why not beware?ميتسي لا تتوهم. وحتى لو كان الأمر كذلك، فلماذا لا تحذر؟
Beware of what?أحذر من ماذا؟
Honestly she didn't explain it to me.بصراحة هي لم توضح لي.
She was distraught when she called.كانت مضطربة حينما اتصلت.
Let's celebrate our happy events and not listen to Misty's warning.دعنا نحتفل بمناسباتنا السعيدة ولا نستمع لتحذير ميستي.
As you like. But I was...مثلما تحب. لكنني كنت...
You wanted to celebrate me as a true hero.كنت تريد ان تحتفل بي كبطل حقيقي.
Who was able to collect the most powerful and rare Pokémons, right?استطاع أن يجمع أقوى البوكيمونات وأندرها، أليس كذلك؟
It is so, Ash, but...هو كذلك يا آش، لكن...
But what?لكن ماذا؟
Ah. See what you've done? The pokeball has fallen.آه. أترى ما فعلت؟ سقطت كرة البوكي.
Calm down Ash, and let's look for it quietly as we sing our favorite song.اهدأ يا آش، ودعنا نبحث عنها بهدوء ونحن نغني أغنية المفضلة.
Where is my ball? In the middle of the field? My ball is gone.أين كرتي؟ وسط الملعب؟ ضاعت كرتي.
How will I play? How will I play?كيف سألعب؟ كيف سألعب؟
I finally found it.أخيرا وجدتها.
I got hurt, Conan. Someone threw a broken bottle.جرحت يا كونان، أحدهم رمى زجاجة مكسورة.
I seriously injured my thumb! My thumb.فجرحت إبهامي جرحا بليغا! إبهامي.
Oh my God, the wound is big.يا إلهي، الجرح كبير.
Give me your handkerchief to put it on the wound.أعطني منديلك لأضعه على الجرح.
Put it on the wound and come with me to cleanse the wound site.ضعه على الجرح وتعالى معي لكي نطهر موضع الجرح.
I'll go for treatment in the hospital.سأذهب للعلاج في المشفى.
And the party?والحفل؟
Please don't tell my Pokémon friends.أرجوك لا تخبر أصدقائي البوكيمونات.
minutes and I'll get back to you. It's nothing big..دقائق وأعود إليكم. الأمر بسيط.
Here, Conan. Sorry about what happened to the handkerchief.خذا يا كونان أسف لما حصل للمنديل.
Never mind. May God bless you. I'll wait for you my friend.لا تهتم وليرعاك الله. سأنتظرك يا صديقي.
This song is dedicated by Pokémons to their friend Ash.وهذه الأغنية مهداة من البوكيمونات إلى صديقهم آش.
On the occasion of his celebration today of winning the title of a true champion.بمناسبة احتفاله اليوم بالحصول على لقب البطل الحقيقي.
Because he was able to collect the best, strongest and rarest Pokémon characters.لأنه استطاع أن يجمع أفضل وأقوى وأندر شخصيات البوكيمونات
With the Pokémon team. This song is dedicated to Ash.مع فريق البوكيمونات. وهذه الأغنية المهداة لـ آش.
(Today we came to sing for Ash. Long live) long live Ash.جئنا اليوم نغني لآش. عاش عاش) عاش آش.
(We came to sing for Ash, long live) long live Ash.جئنا اليوم نغني لآش عاش عاش) عاش آش.
(Did the joy fade out yet? No, no) No it did not.طاش الفرح أم ما طاش) لا ما طاش.
Where is our friend Conan? (Yes, yes Conan?)أين صديقنا يا كونان؟ (نعم، نعم يا كونان؟)
The party has already started, but our friend is gone.بدأ الحفل منذ الآن، لكن صديقنا ما بان.
The party has already started (where is our friend Conan?)بدأ الحفل منذ الآن (أين صديقنا يا كونان؟)
Where is our friend Conan? Yes, yes Conan?)أين صديقنا يا كونان؟ نعم، نعم يا كونان؟)
The party has already started, but our friend is gone.بدأ الحفل منذ الآن، لكن صديقنا ما بان.
The party has already started (where is our friend Conan?)بدأ الحفل منذ الآن (أين صديقنا يا كونان؟)
Actually guys I don't have an answer right now.في الحقيقة يا أصحاب ليس لدي الآن جواب.
What happened, Conan, is he in danger or is he safe?ماذا حدث يا كونان؟ أهو بخطر أم بأمان؟
And what's this, Conan?ثم ما هذا يا كونان؟
In fact in fact... This is... This is...في الحقيقة في الحقيقة... هذا... هذا...
Ash?آش؟
Yes. Yes. Ash has come to penetrate all the woods.نعم. نعم. قد جاء آش مخترقا كل الأحراش.
Let's dance and sing, long live.فلنرقص هيا ونغني، عاش عاش...
Long live Ash.عاش آش.
Yes, Ash has come to penetrate all the woods.نعم، نعم، قد جاء آش مخترقا كل الأحراش.
Let's dance and sing, long live...فلنرقص هيا ونغني عاش عاش...
Long live Ash.عاش آش.
(Today we came to sing for Asg. Long live) long live Ash.جئنا اليوم نغني لآش. عاش عاش) عاش آش.
(Did the joy fade out yet? No, no) No it did not.طاش الفرح أم ما طاش) لا ما طاش.
Here's the important news.إليكم هذا الخبر الهام.
The White Riding Hood gang; James, Jessie, and the bad cat Meowth.قامت عصابة الرداء الأبيض جيم وجيسي والقط الشرير ميوث.
Broke into the children's television station Spacetoon.باقتحام محطة تلفزيون الأطفال سبيستون.
What is strange is that the gang took only the secret file of the station's well-known hero Ash.والغريب أن العصابة لم تأخذ من المحطة إلا الملف السري لبطل المحطة المعروف آش.
Ash?آش؟
Is my file that important for the gang to take it?وهل ملفي مهم إلى هذه الدرجة حتى تستولي عليه العصابة؟
Please shut up Ash. It's dangerous.اصمت من فضلك يا آش فالأمر خطير.
Yes, it's serious.نعم الأمر خطير.
Dear friends. Don't concern yourself with Ash's file.يا أصدقائي الأحبة. لا تشغلوا أنفسكم بملف آش.
I mean my file.أعني ملفي.
It's serious. The file contains all of Ash's secrets.الأمر خطير. فالملف يضم جميع أسرار آش.
As well as the secrets of the power of water, air, electric and herbal Pokémons.وكذلك أسرار قوة البوكيمونات المائية والهوائية والكهربائية والعشبية.
Be careful, my Pokémon friends.إحذروا يا أصدقائي البوكيمونات.
Be careful my friend Ash.إحذر يا صديقي آش.
Conan, Detective, don't ruin my beautiful party. It's nothing big..كونان أيها المحقق لا تفسد حفلي الجميل هذا، الأمر بسيط.
Yes, simple.نعم، بسيط.
So let's get on with our party.إذن فلنكمل حفلنا.
(We came to sing for Ash, long live) long live Ash.جئنا اليوم نغني لآش عاش عاش) عاش آش.
(Did the joy fade out yet? No, no) No it did not.طاش الفرح أم ما طاش) لا ما طاش.
My friends, my friends, even if it is simple, caution is a must.يا أصدقائي، يا أصحابي حتى لو كان الأمر بسيط فالحذر واجب.
What's wrong with you, Ash? I know you are careful what happened to you.ما بك يا آش غير مهتم؟ أعرفك حذر فماذا حدث لك؟
We simply want to have fun playing, dancing and singing.ببساطة نريد أن نفرح نلعب نرقص نغني.
Be careful Ash. Be careful as the wound may bleed.احذر يا آش. احذر فالجرح قد ينزف.
The wound? What wound?الجرح؟ أي جرح؟
Your right thumb was injured. Don't you remember?جرح إبهامك الأيمن. ألا تذكر؟
Where's my ball?أين كرتي؟
Your ball? What ball?كرتك؟ أي كرة؟
Come on, Ash, I lost my ball. Come on Ash.آش ضاعت كرتي. هيا يا آش.
What's this, Conan? We want to be happy, and you ask for your ball.ما هذا يا كونان؟ نريد أن نفرح وأنت تسأل عن كرتك.
Let's party in the Verdian Forest, come on.هيا نحتفل في غابة فيرديان، هيا.
(We came to sing for Ash, long live live) long live Ash.جئنا اليوم نغني لآش عاش عاش) عاش آش.
Please listen to me.أرجوكم استمعوا إليّ أرجوكم.
(Did the joy fade out yet? No, no) No it did not.طاش الفرح أم ما طاش) لا ما طاش.
Please listen to me.أرجوكم استمعوا إلي أرجوك.
I'm not going to let the White Riding Hood gang beat my friends.لن أدع عصابة الرداء الأبيض تنتصر على أصدقائي وتهزمهم.
They have to be saved no matter what it costs me.لا بد من إنقاذهم مهما كلفني الأمر.
Caterpie where are you, Caterpie. Caterpie, my friend.كاتربي أين أنت يا كاتربي. كاتربي يا صديقي.
Caterpie. My friend Caterpie.كاتربي. صديقي كاتربي.
Where are you? Caterpie, where are you?أين أنت؟ كاتربي، أين أنت؟
I'm coming, Ash.أنا قادم يا آش.
But I'm scared, Ash.لكنني خائف يا آش.
Afraid? What are you afraid of?خائف من ماذا تخاف؟
We want to eliminate all insects that harm flowers and weeds.نحن نريد القضاء على كل الحشرات التي تؤذي الأزهار والأعشاب.
But I'm not. No. No.لكنني لا. لا. لا.
My friend, your white cocoon fabric can do it easily.كاتربي يا صديقي نسيج الشرنقة الأبيض الذي تملكه يستطيع فعل ذلك وبسهولة.
But I'm going to kill my beneficial insects friends.لكنني سأقضي على أصدقائي من الحشرات المفيدة.
Pollute our environment, kill the weeds that adorn the face of Mother Earth.وألوث بيئتنا، وأقتل الأعشاب التي تزين وجه أمنا الأرض.
It's okay, Caterpie, it's okay! New weeds will grow later.لا عليك يا كاتربي، لا عليك! ستنمو فيما بعد أعشاب جديدة.
Powerful weeds without bugs, nor pests.أعشاب قوية بلا حشرات. ولا آفات.
Do you think so, Ash?هل تعتقد ذلك يا آش؟
Yes, Caterpie. Let's start spraying the white cocoon fabric immediately.نعم يا كاتربي. هيا فتبدأ برش نسيج الشرنقة الأبيض في الحال.
As you wish, Ash.أمرك يا آش.
Weeds are dead on the planet?الأعشاب ماتت على الكرة الأرضية؟
What a misfortune. What happened?يا للمصيبة. ماذا حدث؟
Please I want to talk to Mr. Akai, the Pokémon trainer.من فضلك أريد التحدث مع الأستاذ أكاي مدرب البوكيمونات.
Professor Akay! This is Detective Conan.الأستاذ أكاي! معك المحقق كونان.
There has been a stormy attack on Mother Earth. The weeds are dead. What do you say? Unreasonable?حدث هجوم عاصف على أمنا الأرض. الأعشاب ماتت. ماذا تقول؟ غير معقول؟
I have no strength anymore, Ash. My strength weakened after I lost my fabric.لم يعد لدي قوة يا آش. ضعفت قوتي بعد أن فقدتُ نسيجي.
Hold me, Ash, please.احملني يا آش أرجوك.
I beg you to help me. Please.أتوسل إليك ساعدني. أرجوك.
Don't be afraid my friend Caterpie. Don't be afraid.لا تخف يا صديقي كاتبري. لا تخف.
I'll take you to my house to rest.سوف آخذك إلى بيتي لترتاح.
Come enter my pokeball and your strength will replenish soon.تعال لتدخل إلى كرة البوكي وستعود إليك قوتك عما قريب.
Come on, my beautiful friend.هيا يا صديقي الجميل هيا.
Come on my friend. Come on.هيا يا صديقي هيا.
We love flowers and we love trees.نحن نحب الأزهار ونحب الأشجار.
We've eliminated the first sections of life on Earth.لقد قضينا على أول أقسام الحياة على الكرة الأرضية.
We'll make them eliminate everything.سنجعلهم يقضون على كل شيء.
So we establish our control over the Earth.وبذلك نحكم سيطرتنا على الأرض.
And own everything, even rats. I love rats so much.ونملك كل شيء حتى الفئران. كم أحب الفئران.
You idiot. You idiot, you hurt me.أيها الغبي. أيها الغبي، لقد جرحتني.
I'll tear you apart, punk.سأمزققك أيها الشرير.
Meowth, this is enough! Enough, you idiots. There's someone coming.ميوث كفى! كفى أيها الغبيان. هنالك أحد قادم.
Let's run before they find out about us. Come on.هيا نهرب قبل أن يكتشفوا أمرنا. هيا.
Bad guys! The bad guys killed the weeds. They killed grass and flowers. They destroyed our environment.الأشرار! الأشرار قتلوا الأعشاب. قتلوا الأعشاب والأزهار. دمروا بيئتنا.
Pika! Pika!بيكا بيكا!
Long live, long live Ash.آش عاش عاش آش.
Pikachu! What are you doing here?بيكاتشو! ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I came to collect flowers.جئت لأجمع زهورًا.
Flowers?زهور؟
Our friend Caterpie is sick. I want to visit him with a bouquet of flowers.صديقنا كاتربي مريض. أريد أن أزوره ومعي باقة ورد.
Caterpie is sick? Sick?كاتربي مريض؟ مريض؟
Caterpie is a type of green worm Pokemon. Its power lies in the white cocoon fabric.البوكيمون كاتربي نوع الدود الأخضر، قوته تكمن في نسيج الشرنقة الأبيض.
Oh now I know everything. But why would the good Caterpie do that?آه الآن عرفت كل شيء. لكن لماذا يفعل كاتربي الطيب ذلك؟
Why? Why?لماذا؟ لماذا؟
Pika! Pika!Conan Conan! What is this?بيكا بيكا! كونان كونان! ما هذا؟
All flowers are dead what happened?جميع الزهور ميتة ماذا حدث؟
There is a mystery that only Conan will solve.هنالك لغز لن يحله إلا كونان.
(Let's play! Let's play! We always play and never get tired.)هيا نلعب! هيا نلعب! نلعب دومًا لا لا نتعب.)
Throw the ball to me and let it jump, end up, go down.ارمي الكرة إلي ودعها تقفز تبرم تعلو تنزل.
But don't let her run away (we always play, we don't get tired).لكن لا تجعلها تهرب (نلعب دوما لا لا نتعب).
(Let's play! Let's play! We always play and never get tired.)هيا نلعب! هيا نلعب! نلعب دومًا لا لا نتعب.)
I also know how to count.إني عارفة بالعد أيضا شاطرةٌ بالصد.
One, two and I jump and the stadium applauds me (we always play, we don't get tired).واحد اثننان وأعدي دوما ويصفق لي الملعب (نلعب دوما لا لا نتعب).
Come on Pokemons, come on! To stop, to get up.هيا بوكيموناتي هيا! أن تتوقف أن تقم.
Night came after morning. Now it's time to go to sleep.جاء الليل بعد الصبح. حان الآن وقت النوم.
Come on Pokemons come on! To stop, to get up.هيا بوكيموناتي هيا! أن تتوقف أن تقم.
Night came after morning. Now it's bedtime.جاء الليل بعد الصبح. حان الآن وقت نوم.
We don't want to sleep even if it gets dark.لا نريد أن ننام حتى لو جاء الظلام.
Oh it’s better to play than all the words (we always play, we don't get tired).آه ما أحلى اللعب خير من كل الكلام (نلعب دوما لا لا نتعب).
(Let's play, let's play, always play, and don't get tired)هيا نلعب، هيا نلعب، نلعب دومًا لا لا نتعب)
We love all the kids in the world.نحن نحب كل أطفال العالم.
We grow roses everywhere.ونزرع الورود في كل مكان.
We hate hatred and cultivate love.ونكره الحقد ونزرع المحبة.
To make your dreams come true join.لتحقيق أحلامكم انضموا إلى.
Jessie.جيسي.
James.جيمس.
Join our gang or get ready to fight.انضموا إلى عصابتنا أو استعدوا للقتال.
JOIN, JOIN!انضموا، انضموا!
Our plan worked! We are so happy.نجحت خطتنا! يا لفرحتنا.
We'll announce our second step. The turn came on the air.وسنعلن ثاني خطواتنا. جاء الدور على الهواء.
We killed Greenery. Really at all.قتلنا الخضرة. فعلا بالمرة.
We're having the best evening tonight and planning to pollute the water.نقضي الليلة أحلى سهرة ونخطط تلويث الماء.
So beautiful. We didn't get a response.جميلٌ جدًا. لم نلقى ردًا.
We're going to pollute this land, cut off its electricity.سوف نلوث هذه الأرض، نقطع عنها الكهرباء.
Our plan worked. We are so happy!نجحت خطتنا. يا لفرحتنا!
We'll announce our second steps. The turn came on the air.وسنعلن ثاني خطواتنا. جاء الدور على الهواء.
The turn came on the air. The turn came on the air. The turn came on the air.جاء الدور على الهواء. جاء الدور على الهواء. جاء الدور على الهواء.
We love flowers.نحب الأزهار.
And we love trees.ونحب الأشجار.
To make your dreams come true, join.لتحقيق أحلامكم انضموا إلى.
Jesse.جيسي.
James.جيمس.
Join our gang or get ready to fight.انضموا إلى عصابتنا أو استعدوا للقتال.
JOIN! JOIN!انضموا! انضموا!
Meowth, shut up!
ميوث! اسكت!
Someone is coming.هناك أحد قادم.
Come on, James.تعال يا جيمس.
Do I wonder who are they?ترى من هو؟
Oh God, where are we going to hide?يا ويلي أين سنختبئ؟
Let's go hide.هيا بنا نختبئ.
You stepped on my tail, get away, get away! Oh God.دعست على ذيلي، ابتعد، ابتعد! يا ويلي.
Meowth shut up.ميوث اسكت.
Pikachu! Where are you friends? Pikachu, Caterpie? Where are you two?بيكاتشو! أين أنتم يا أصدقاء؟ بيكاتشو، كاتربي؟ أين أنتما؟
We got him.لقد وقع.
What's this?ما هذا؟
Did we scare you, Ash?أخفت يا آش؟
I... No I didn't.أنا... لا لم أخف.
You coward! Are you that scared?يا جبان! أنت خائف إلى هذا الحد؟
No. No. It's just that I'm afraid that someone will find out.لا. لا. كل ما في الأمر أنني أخاف أن يكشفن أحد.
What? No. No. Rest assured that no one will find out... Ash.ماذا؟ لا. لا. اطمئن لن يكشفك أحٌد يا... يا آش.
I'm afraid of Detective Conan.أنا خائف من المحقق كونان.
Detective Conan?المحقق كونان؟
Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid. He'll never suspect you.لا تخاف. لا تخاف. لن يشك بك أبدًا.
I hope we're quick to implement the rest of our plan.أرجو أن نسرع في تنفيذ باقي خطتنا.
Yes, yes! We love the children of the world.نعم، نعم! نحن نحب أطفال العالم.
We grow roses everywhere.ونزرع الورود في كل مكان.
We hate hatred and cultivate love.نكره الحقد ونزرع المحبة.
To make your dreams come true join...لتحقيق أحلامكم انضموا إلى...
Jessie.جيسي.
James.جيمس.
Join the White Riding Hood Gang.انضموا إلى عصابة الرداء الأبيض.
Join our gang or get ready to fight.انضموا إلى عصابتنا أو استعدوا للقتال.
JOIN! JOIN!انضموا! انضموا!
Calm down, calm down! Please be quiet.اهدؤوا، اهدؤوا! بهدوء، أرجوكم بهدوء.
Okay. Come on Ash, come and listen to our new plan.حسنًا. تعالى يا آش، تعالى واسمع خطتنا الجديدة.
Never.أبدا لا.
No no.لا لا.
No. Unbelievable.لا غير معقول.
Pika. Pika Pika.بيكا. بيكا بيكا.
Ash? Ash’s with the White Riding Hood Gang?آش؟ آش مع عصابة الرداء الأبيض؟
ItThat's weird. Pika Pika.أمر غريب. بيكا بيكا.
I wonder what is Ash doing with the gang?ترى ماذا يفعل آش مع العصابة؟
Calm down! Calm down! Calm down or you will expose us.اهدؤوا! اهدؤوا! اهدؤوا وإلا فضحتمونا.
You'll wake up the whole forest.ستوقظون الغابة كلها.
They love kids and roses. You only love destruction.يحبون الأطفال والورود. أنتم لا تحبون إلا الدمار.
Ash! Ash! Don't forget that you... And that we...آش! آش! لا تنسى أنك... وأننا...
No I haven't forgotten. Go ahead and complete your plan. But while whispering.لا لم أنسى. هيا أكملوا خطتكم. ولكن بهمس.
Okay, Ash. While whispering. We get it.حسنا. يا آش. بهمس. لك ما تريد.
Our plan, my dear Ash, is... Listen...خطتنا يا عزيزي آش هي... اسمع...
I told you to whisper. Whisper, Meowth.قلت لك بهمس. بمهس يا ميوث.
Please, quietly.بهدوء أرجوكم.
Shut up! He told you quitly.اصمت! قال لك بهدوء.
in a whisper.بهمس.
Okay, Ash.حسنا يا آش.
Take this and do the rest of the plan written in this paper.خذ هذا ونفذ باقي الخطة المكتوبة في هذه الورقة.
Come on! Bye Ash! While whispering.هيا! ودعًا يا آش! وبهمس.
Whisper, Ash.بهمس يا آش.
Pika! Pika!بيكا بيكا.
What are you doing in the forest at this time, Ash?آش ماذا تفعل في الغابة في مثل هذا الوقت؟
Pikachu, what are you doing here?بيكاتشو، أنت ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Me?أنا؟
Oh I forgot. I forgot that the forest is your home. How lucky!آه نسيت. نسيت أن الغابة هي بيتك. يا لحظي الجميل!
Did you know that I was coming to visit Pidgiotto.هل تعلم أنني كنت قادما لزيارة بيدجيوتوه.
Coming to visit Pidjyotoh, or to meet the White Riding hood Gang?قادم لزيارة بيدجيوتوه، أم للقائ عصابة الرداء الأبيض؟
Do you befriend enemies? Who want to destroy the Earth and kill all Pokémon?أنت يا آش تصادق الأعداء؟ تصادق من يريد تدمير الأرض وخرابها وقتل جميع البوكيمونات؟
Poor Pikachu, this is my plan to take down the gang.مسكين يا بيكاتشو، تلك خطتي للقضاء على العصابة.
Pika.بيكا.
They thought I became their friend after I decieved them.لقد ظنوا بأنني أصبحت صديقهم بعد أن خدعتهم.
Pika Pika.بيكا بيكا.
and you'll see what happens in the end.وسترى ماذا يحدث في النهاية.
Pika! Pika!بيكا بيكا.
I'm sorry, Ash.أنا آسف يا آش.
It's okay.لا عليك.
Pika pika pika pika.بيكا بيكا بيكا بيكا.
Pikachu!بيكاتشو!
Pika?بيكا؟
Where are you going at this time?إلى أين أنت ذاهب في مثل هذا الوقت؟
I'll go back to sleep to wake up early in the morning, Pika! Pika!سأعود إلى النوم ثانية حتى أصحو في الصباح الباكر، بيكا بيكا.
Pikachu.بيكاتشو.
Pika! Pika!بيكا بيكا.
I want you to wake Pidgiotto right now.أريدك أن توقظ بيدجيوتوه الآن.
This late?في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
Yes, to sabotage the gang's plan.نعم، كي نخرب خطة العصابة.
As long as that's the case. I'll wake him up right away. Pika Pika.ما دام الأمر كذلك. سأقوظه حالا. بيكا بيكا.
You scared me.لقد أفزعتموني.
Have you implemented the plan?هل نفذت الخطة؟
Please get out before you expose us.أرجوكم أخرجوا قبل أن يفضح أمرنا.
Are you afraid, Ash?أنت خائف يا آش؟
Yes, I'm afraid.نعم، خائف.
Very afraid.خائفٌ جدا.
I hear a sound.أسمع صوتا.
What?ماذا؟
Please hide.اختبئوا أرجوكم.
Let's hide here, come on.هيا لنختبئ هنا، هيا.
Ash! Ash!آش! آش!
Pidjiutoh, come here.بيدجيوتوه، تعال إلى هنا.
Pikachu told me you wanted me right away. Is it serious?قال لي بيكاتشو إنك تريدني وحالا. هل الأمر خطير؟
Yes, very serioys, Pidgeotto.نعم خطير جدا يا بيدجيوتوه.
Listen.اسمع.
Why?لماذا؟
Really? Okay. Well, I'll call my Pokémon friends.حقا؟ حسنا. حسنا، سوف نادي أصدقائي البوكيمونات.
Squirtel, Caterpie, Horsy, Charmillion, Exquiter.سكويرل، كاتربي، هورسي، تشارميليون، إكسكيوتر.
Pedri, Mr Mind.بيدري، مستر مايند.
Come on Pokémons, spray this stuff all over the forest.هيا أيتها البوكيمونات، رشوا هذه المادة في كل الغابة.
Ash, this is a dangerous substance.آش هذه المادة خطرة.
which will pollute the air. We might die.ستلوث الهواء. وقد نموت.
No. No, Pokémons. This substance will form hidden mesh.لا. لا أيتها البوكيمونات. هذه المادة ستكون شبكًا مخفيًا.
To prevent the White Riding Hood gang vehicle from flying in the air. So we could catch them.يمنع مركبة عصابة الرداء الأبيض من الانطلاق في الجو. فنصطادهم.
The White Riding Hood Gang will finally fall into our hands.أخيرا ستقع عصابة الرداء الأبيض بأيدينا.
Let's start your work before the gang wake up and expose our plan.هيا ابدأوا عملكم قبل أن تستيقظ العصابة من نومها فتكشف خطتنا.
The air. Earth's air has become polluted. What a misfortune.الهواء. هواء الأرض أصبح ملوثا. مصيبة.
Something serious is happening.هنالك أمر خطير يحدث.
Carbon powder pollutes the air and increases the ozone hole.مسحوق الكربون يقوم بتلويث الهواء ويزيد من ثقب الأوزون.
If the ozone hole expands, we'll all be at risk. The more pollution, the greater the danger.إذا اتسع ثقب الأوزون سنتعرض جميعا للخطر. كلما ازداد التلوث كلما زاد الخطر.
Pikachu. What's it, all the water?بيكاتشو. ماذا هناك؟ المياه جميعها؟
What do you say? Ash is he talking to the White Riding Hood gang.ماذا تقول؟ آش يحادث عصابة الرداء الأبيض.
The water was contaminated with waste and black ink?تلوثت المياه بالنفايات والحبر الأسود؟
Oh my God, Pikachu! Black ink? I think I know the reason.مصيبة يا بيكاتشو! الحبر الأسود؟ أظنني عرفت السبب.
I'll call you later Pikachu. Let's see what the computer says.سأتصل بك فيما بعد يا بيكاتشو. لنر ما ذا يقول الحاسوب.
Horsy the sea horse is a peaceful aquatic animal, but when it gets angry, it spits black ink into the water and pollutes it.	هورسي  حصان البحر حيوان مائي مسالم، لكنه حين يغضب يقوم ببسق الحبر الأسود في الماء وتلويثه.
But why would the good horsy do that? I must know the secret.لكن لماذا يفعل هورسي الطيب ذلك؟ في الأمر سر يجب أن أعرفه.
The greenery was killed. The air is polluted. The water is polluted.قتلت الخضرة. تلوث الهواء. تلوث الماء.
What's left for us? Huh. What is this?ماذا بقي لنا؟ هاه. ما هذا؟
Where is your attention, Conan. Where is your wit?أين نباهتك يا كونان. أين شطارتك؟
You must uncover the secret. Come on, Conan. Come on.لا بد أن تعرف حل اللغز. هيا يا كونان. هيا.
Our flowers are dead, even the weeds. It died and the earth is back to ruins.أزهارنا ماتت، حتى الأعشاب. ماتت والعصبة عادت في الأرض خراب.
We are without water. And the air is black.صرنا بلا ماء. واسود الهواء.
No electricity and the lights are black.لا كهرباء والأضواء صارت سوداء.
Our flowers are dead, even the weeds. It died and the earth is back to ruins.أزهارنا ماتت، حتى الأعشاب. ماتت والعصبة عادت في الأرض خراب.
No, no, no, my friends. We still have hope.لا لا لا يا أصحابي فالأمل لدينا ما زال.
So far my energy is at its best.والطاقة عندي ما زالت حتى الآن في أحسن حال.
(So far we’re holding up, we still have hope.)حتى الآن بأحسن حال، والأمل لدينا ما زال.)
So far we’re holding up, (we still have hope).حتى الآن بأحسن حال، والأمل لدينا ما زال.)
What a joy! The forest was destroyed and it didn't ruin my hair styling.يا لفرحتي! تدمرت الغابة ولم يخرب تصفيف شعري.
James, James stay away from my tail. I'll jump after that mouse.جيمس جيمس ابتعد عن ذيلي. سأقفز وراء ذلك الفأر.
Meowth, you hit me on the stomach.ميوث لقد ضربتني على بطني.
Meowth. Stay away from me!!ميوث. ابتعد عني
Calm down, they’ll catch us.اهدؤوا اهدؤوا، سيقضح أمرنا.
Pikachu what will your card do?بيكاتشو ماذا ستفعل بطاقتك؟
Pika Pika! An electric-powered water filter.بيكا بيكا مصفاة للماء تعمل بالطاقة الكهربائية.
Powered by electricity?تعمل بالطاقة الكهربائية؟
Bad air extractors are also powered by electricity.وشفاطات الهواء الفاسد تعمل بالطاقة الكهربائية أيضًا.
If the water is filtered and the air is purified. Pollution will be removed from all things.وإذا صفي الماء ونقي الهواء. زال التلوث عن كل الأشياء.
From all things?عن كل الأشياء؟
Pekka! Pika! (Pika! Pika!)بيكا بيكا (بيكا بيكا).
Now I'm going to direct my electric power towards the filter and the purifiers to work again.والآن سأوجه طاقتي الكهربائية نحو المصفاة والشفاطات لتعمل ثانية.
Pika! Pika!بيكا بيكا.
Long live Ash.آش عاش عاش آش.
Ash, please! My Pokémon friends please! Now is not the time to play.آش أرجوك! أصحابي البوكيمونات أرجوكم! ليس الآن وقت اللعب.
Pikachu my dear friend. Let's play.بيكاتشو يا صديقي العزيز. دعنا نلعب.
This’s strange, Ash. Don't you see the destruction that has befallen the land?أمرك غريب يا آش. ألا ترى الدمار الذي حل بالأرض؟
Things will get better if you listen to my advice.الأمور ستصبح أحسن لو سمعتم نصيحتي.
Go ahead my friend. Time is short.تفضل يا صديقي فالوقت ضيق.
Everything is corrupt here. Isn't that the case?كل شيء أصبح فاسدا هنا. أليس الأمر كذلك؟
Indeed.هو كذلك.
The earth has been contaminated.الأرض تلوثت.
Contaminated?تلوثت؟
The flowers, the fish and the weeds and everything beautiful are dead.وماتت الأزهار والأسماك والأعشاب وكل شيء جميل.
Everything beautiful?كل شيء جميل؟
Pika! Pika! But the power is still there. We will get everything back to the way it is if we work together.بيكا بيكا! ولكن الطاقة الكهربائية ما زالت. وسنعيد كل شيء إلى حاله لو تعاوننا معا.
No. No. I have the solution.لا. لا. الحل عندي.
What is it, my dear friend?ما هو يا صديقي العزيز؟
I was able to trick the White Riding Hood gang and take the key to operate their spacecraft from them.استطعت أن أخدع عصابة الرداء الأبيض وأخذ منهم مفتاح تشغيل مركبتهم الفضائية.
Pika! Pika!بيكا بيكا.
Continue my beloved friend.أكمل يا صديقي الحبيب.
We'll all go to the ship and go to another planet.سنذهب جميعا إلى المركبة ونتوجه لكوكب آخر.
Another planet?كوكبٍ آخر؟
What about Earth?والأرض؟
It's no longer useful. We'll leave it to the gang and it's ruined.ما عادت تفيد، سنتركها للعصابة وهي خراب.
How can we give up my homeland, my friend?وكيف نتخلى عن وطني يا صديقي؟
How, my friend?كيف يا صديقنا؟
This is not our friend Ash.آش هذا ليس بصديقنا.
What?ماذا؟
Yes, this is a criminal.نعم، هذا مجرم.
You want to ruin what's between me and my friends? I'm your friend.تريد أن تخرب ما بيني وبين أصدقائي؟ أنا صديقكم.
Yes, Ash's our friend.نعم، آش صديقنا.
No. No. Did he not ask Caterpie to kill greenery and flowers?كلا. كلا. ألم يطلب من كاتربي قتل الخضرة والأزهار؟
And horsy to pollute the water and Picchu to pollute the air?ومن هورس تلويث المياه ومن بيتشو إفساد الهواء؟
Yes, yes.أجل، أجل.
I wanted to give them a new life.كنت أريد أن نوفر لهم حياة جديدة.
Don't let him deceive you. He is a criminal.لا يخدعكم. إنه مجرم.
WhatAsh is a criminal?آش مجرم؟
Do you believe that I'm a criminal?هل تصدقون أنني مجرم؟
Agh, Long live Ash.آش عاش. عاش آش.
Ash, Long live Ash.آش عاش. عاش آش.
Don't let him deceive you. This isn't Ash.لا يخدعكم. هذا ليس آش.
What are you saying?ماذا تقول؟
Conan’s gone crazy. I'm sure Conan’s gone crazy.جن كونان. أنا متأكد من أن كونان جن.
This is Ash, this is not Ash. This is Ash, this is not Ash.هذا آش، هذا ليس آش. هذا آش، هذا ليس آش.
Conan’s gone crazy. Go ahead and arrest him.جن كونان. أنا متأكد من أن كونان جن.
Did you believe him? He is a criminal, arrest him.هل صدقتموه؟ إنه مجرم، اقبضوا عليه.
He is the criminal, arrest him.بل هو المجرم، اقبضوا عليه.
Who do we arrest? This is hard.على من نقبض؟ هذا صعب.
This is the criminal.هذا هو المجرم.
Wait my friends. Conan didn't offend us but Ash's behavior has been weird lately.لحظة يا أصدقائي. كونان لم يسئ إلينا ولكن تصرفات آش كانت غريبة في الآونة الأخيرة.
Me? He's the criminal.أنا؟ هو المجرم.
Tell me, Ash. Why is Conan a criminal?قل لي آش. لماذا تعد كونان مجرما؟
Because he's trying to keep us apart.لأنه يحاول أن يفرق بيننا.
There is something that will settle the matter.هنالك أمر سيحسم الموضوع.
What is it, Conan.ما هو يا كونان.
Can you take off your gloves.هل يمكن أن تخلع قفازيك.
Hahahahahaha. Take it off? Here are my gloves.هههههههههههه أخلعها؟ ها هما قفازي.
Raise your right hand up.ارفع يدك اليمنى إلى الأعلى.
Raise my hand? Why?أرفع يدي؟ لماذا؟
Please, Ash, raise it up! Let's see what Conan has.أرجوك يا آش، ارفعها! لنرى ما الذي لدى كونان.
This is my right hand raised.وهذه يدي اليمنى مرفوعة.
Pikachu! Check Ash's hand. Is there a wound on it?بيكاتشو! افحص يد آش. هل هناك جرح بها؟
No wound, not even a trace of it.لا جرح ولا حتى أي أثر لجرح.
Arrest him immediately. This isn't the real Ash.اقبضوا عليه في الحال. هذا ليس آش الحقيقي.
This is fake Ash.هذا آش المزيف.
What?ماذا؟
Because my thumb is not injured I became fake? What a joke!لأن إبهامي غير مجروح أصبحت مزيفا؟ يا للسخرية!
Don't you remember the handkerchief you found in the trash at the house on the day of the party?ألا تتذكر المنديل الذي وجدته في سلة المهملات في بيت يوم الاحتفال؟
Yes, I remember it was full of blood. What's about it?أجل أتذكره كان مشبعا بالدماء، ما به؟
That was the blood of Ash who had a big wound that day.كانت تلك دماء آش الذي جرح ذلك اليوم جرحًا كبيرًا.
The scars of the wound do not go away for at least two weeks.وآثار الجرح لا تزول قبل أسبوعين في أقل الأحوال.
True, this is true.صحيح، هذا الكلام صحيح.
Could it be?هل يعقل؟
So this is fake Ash.هذا إذن آش المزيف.
No. Don't believe him! He is the one who is lying, he is a liar. He's the fake one.لا. لا تصدقوه! هو من يكذب، إنه كاذب. هو المزيف.
You're the fake one. Where is the real Ash, criminal?بل أنت المزيف. أين آش الحقيقي يا مجرم؟
I'm Ash, I'm Ash.أنا آش، أنا آش.
He’s Ash?هو آش؟
Not Ash.ليس آش.
Not Ash?ليس بآش؟
Was it...هل كان...
How did this happen? Where is Ash?كيف حدث هذا؟ أين آش؟
I will settle it. Do you guys know the song “Where's My Ball” that we sing with Pokemon balls?أنا أحسم الموضوع. هل تعرفون يا أصحابي أغنية أين كرتي التي نغنيها مع كرات البوكيمون؟
We sing a part and whoever claims to be Ash sings the other part.نغني نحن مقطعًا ويغني من يدعي بأنه آش المقطع الآخر.
Then we'll decide what do you think?وبعدها نقرر ما رأيكم؟
We agree.موافقون.
And yo... Ash.وأنت يا... يا آش.
Huh me? I’ll sing.هاه أنا؟ نغني.
Now get started, my friends. Where's my ball?والآن ابدأوا يا أصحابي. أين كرتي؟
In the field.وسط الملعب.
My ball is gone.ضاعت كرتي.
Go on, Ash.أكمل يا آش.
In the field.وسط الملعب.
In the field, huh? Go on, guys.وسط الملعب هاه؟ أكملوا يا أصحابي.
My ball is gone.ضاعت كرتي.
How will I play?كيف سألعب؟
So, arrest him?اقبضوا عليه إذن؟
Where is our friend Ash? Where is he now?أين صديقنا آش؟ أين هو الآن؟
Enough lying. The White Riding Hood gang has replaced our friend Ash with a fake Ash.كفى كذبًا. لقد استبدلت عصابة الرداء الأبيض صديقنا آش بآش مزيف.
No, no.لا لا.
Shub the bad guy?شوب الشرير؟
Now where is Ash, you criminal?والآن أين آش أيها المجرم؟
In the vehicle, the White Riding Hood Gang vehicle.في المركبة، مركبة عصابة الرداء الأبيض.
The White Riding Hood Gang? We'll catch them.عصابة الرداء الأبيض؟ سوف نقبض عليهم.
James, we’re going to get arrested my friend.جيمس سيقبض علينا يا صديقي.
Let's run away, come on.هيا بنا نهرب، هيا.
Did you hear what I heard? Run away.أسمعتم ما سمعت؟ اهربوا اهربوا.
Oh my God!يا ويلي!
Take me with you!خذيني معك!
Use your electric power, Pikachu!استخدم طاقتك الكهربائية بيكاتشو!
We finally caught you criminals, and the fake Ash is with you.وأخيرًا قبضنا عليكم أيها المجرمون، ومعكم آش المزيف.
And now, guys.والآن يا أصدقاء.
Let's celebrate Ash's return and bring life back to Earth.هيا نحتفل بعودة آش ونعيد الحياة إلى الأرض.
(Today we came to sing for Ash, long live) long live Ash.جئنا اليوم نغني لآش، عاش عاش) عاش آش.
(Did the joy fade out yet? No, no) No it did not.طاش الفرح أم ما طاش) لا ما طاش.
Where is our friend, Conan? (Yes, yes, Conan)أين صديقنا يا كونان؟ (نعم، نعم يا كونان)
The party has already started but our friend is gone.بدأ الحفل منذ الآن لكن صديقنا ما بان.
The party has already started (where is our friend, Conan).بدأ الحفل منذ الآن (أين صديقنا يا كونان).
Yes, yes, Ash has come to penetrate all the woods.نعم، نعم قد جاء آش مخترقا كل الأحراش.
Come on, let's dance and sing, long live (long live Ash)فلنرقص هيا ونغني عاش، عاش (عاش آش)
Today we came to sing to Ash, long live (long live Ash).جئنا اليوم نغني لآش، عاش عاش (عاش آش).
(Did the joy fade out yet? No, no) No it did not.طاش الفرح أم ما طاش) لا ما طاش.
Thank you my friends. Thank you, Conan.شكرا لكم يا أصدقائي. شكرا لك يا كونان.
Without your attention and caution, you would not have solved the puzzle.لولا نباهتك وحذرك ما توصلتم لحل اللغز.
If it wasn't for your concern for the environment and lifting the broken bottle from the ground, we wouldn't have known the real criminal.ولولا اهتمامك بالبيئة ورفعك الزجاجة المكسورة من الأرض، ما عرفنا المجرم الحقيقي.
Let's set that aside. Now what do you got, Ash.دعونا من هذا الحديث. والآن ماذا لديك يا آش.
Let's celebrate your victory by bringing together so many of our Pokémon friends.لنحتفل بانتصارك بجمع كل هذا العدد الكبير من أصدقائنا البوكيمونات.
On such a happy occasion. Ash's return to you and the safety of our beloved land.في مثل هذه المناسبة السعيدة. عودة آش إليكم وسلامة أرضنا الحبيبة.
And the return of a beautiful life to it thanks to everyone's cooperation.وعودة الحياة الجميلة إليها بفضل تعاون الجميع.
The Spacetoon children's TV station is pleased to offer you and all the children who are with us this song.يسر محطة الأطفال سبيستون أن تقدم لكم ولجميع الأطفال الموجودين معنا هذه الأغنية.
Around the globe, around the globe, I’ve been all around the globe.طول وعرض، طول وعرض درت الدنيا طول وعرض.
Around the globe, around the globe, He’s been all around the globe.طول وعرض، طول وعرض دار الدنيا طول وعرض.
I've never seen more beautiful than my homeland. My mother Earth.لم أبصر أجمل من وطني هذه الحلوة أمي الأرض.
There has never been more beautiful than my homeland. My mother Earth.لم يبصر أجمل من وطني هذه الحلوة أمي الأرض.
Around the globe, around the globe, I’ve been all around the globe.طول وعرض، طول وعرض درت الدنيا طول وعرض.
Around the globe, around the globe, He’s been all around the globe.طول وعرض، طول وعرض دار الدنيا طول وعرض.
As long as we love it, my friend, let's protect it.ما دمنا نحبها يا صاحبي فلنحميها.
from every enemy or thing that might hurt it.من كل عدو أو شيء قد يؤذيها.
For the sake of water (and don't waste).من أجل الماء (لا نسرف).
We grow flowers (and don't damage).نزرع أزهارًا (لا نتلف).
We save our energy.نحفظ طاقتنا.
We nurture our smile.نرعى بسمتنا.
We grow our vegetables and love the earth.نزرع خضرتنا ونحب الأرض.
Around the globe, around the globe, I’ve been all around the globe.طول وعرض، طول وعرض درت الدنيا طول وعرض.
Around the globe, around the globe, He’s been all around the globe.طول وعرض، طول وعرض دار الدنيا طول وعرض.
I've never seen more beautiful than my homeland. My mother Earth.لم أبصر أجمل من وطني هذه الحلوة أمي الأرض.
Mother Earth, Mother Earth, Long live Mother Earth.أمي الأرض، أمي الأرض، عاشت عاشت أمي الأرض.
I always dream of being the best of all.أحلم دومًا أن أكون، الأفضل بين الجميع.
So I gather your Pokémon. As best as I can.لذا أجمع البوكيمون على خير الصنيع.
I always dream of being the best of all.أحلم دوما أن أكون الأفضل بين الجميع.
I'll travel across the Earth looking everywhere.سأسافر عبر الأرض باحثًا في كل مكان.
For Pokémon, the tool of peace, the unrelenting force (Pokémon I will collect it now).عن بوكيمون أداة السلام قوةٌ لا تهان (بوكيمون سأجمعها الآن).
Support me, with your strength help me (Pokémon).فلتساندني، بقوتك ساعدني (بوكيمون).
Oh to our only dream of a new world (Pokémon, I'll collect it now).آه لحلمنا الوحيد نحو عالمٍ جديد (بوكيمون، سأجمعها الآن).
To support goodness.لنصرة الخير.
To rebel evil from others.لدحر الشر عن الغير.
Teach me, and take Pokémon from me (Pokémon).علمني، وخذ مني بوكيمون (بوكيمون).
I always dream of being the best of all.أحلم دوما أن أكون الأفضل بين الجميع.
So I gather your Pokémon. As best as I can.لذا أجمع البوكيمون على خير الصنيع.
I'll travel across the Earth looking everywhere.سأسافر عبر الأرض باحثًا في كل مكان.
For Pokémon, the tool of peace, the unrelenting force (Pokémon I will collect it now).عن بوكيمون أداة السلام قوةٌ لا تهان (بوكيمون سأجمعها الآن).
Support me, with your strength help me (Pokémon).فلتساندني، بقوتك ساعدني (بوكيمون).
Oh to our only dream of a new world (Pokémon, I'll collect it now).آه لحلمنا الوحيد نحو عالمٍ جديد (بوكيمون، سأجمعها الآن).
To support goodness.لنصرة الخير.
To rebel evil from others.لدحر الشر عن الغير.
Teach me, and take Pokémon from me (Pokémon).علمني، وخذ مني بوكيمون (بوكيمون).
I'll collect it now (Pokémon).سأجمعها الآن (بوكيمون).